Eloise Hubbard Linscott collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series III: Graphic Materials, 200 black-and-white photos, 30 film negatives
  - Subseries C: Itemized list of photographs
    - George (Rocky Mountain George) Brown, holding a rifle (?), with Leroy (Roy) Parris at far left; photographed from inside a car, November 16, 1941, 1 negative: 2.5 x 1.75 in.; afc1942002_ph015
    - George (Rocky Mountain George) Brown, in profile, gesturing with right arm, November 16, 1941, 1 negative: 2.5 x 1.75 in.; afc1942002_ph016
    - Clarice Carr, one of the Shaker Singers of Enfield, New Hampshire, standing by a chair, circa 1948, 1 print: gelatin silver; 2.5 x 2.75 in.; afc1942002_ph017
      Location: Enfield, New Hapmpshire. The Shaker Singers were founded to keep Shaker folklore and singing traditions alive, although none of the members were Shaker.
    - Frank Cates, holding a fiddle and bow at his side, November 8, 1941, 1 negative: 2.5 x 1.75 in.; afc1942002_ph018
      Location: Rockland, Maine.
    - Frank Cates, playing the fiddle, November 8, 1941, 1 negative: 2.5 x 1.75 in.; afc1942002_ph019
    - L.M. Chase, undated, 1 photomechanical print: 5.25 x 3 in.; afc1942002_ph020
      Location: Sebago Lake, Maine. Handwritten note on reverse: "Standish - ME-"
    - Lillian M. Cheney, April 18, 1943, 1 negative: 1.75 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph021
    - Edson H. Cole, seated, holding fiddle and bow, undated, 1 negative: 4.25 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph022
      Location: Freedom, New Hampshire.
    - Edson H. Cole, seated, poised to play fiddle, undated, 1 negative: 4.25 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph023
    - Lois A. Comstock, standing on porch of a house, September 24, 1946, 1 negative: 4.25 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph024
      Location: Clarksville, New Hampshire.
    - Mrs. Crosby (Portrait 1 of 2), March 1943, 1 negative: 1.75 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph025
      Location: Jamaica Plain, Massachusetts.
    - Mrs. Crosby (Portrait 2 of 2), March 1943, 1 negative: 2.75 x 1.75 in.; afc1942002_ph026
    - Agnes E. Deane, leaning back in chair, April 23, 1941, 1 print: gelatin silver; 1.75 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph027
      Location: Walker Street, Taunton, Massachusetts.
    - Agnes E. Deane, leaning forward in chair, April 23, 1941, 1 negative: 1.75 x 2.75 in.; afc1942002_ph028
    - Herbert D. (Bert) Farnham, with young girl in background, July 1941, 1 print: 2.5 x 3.5 in.; afc1942002_ph029
      Typed note on reverse: "[t]aken July '41 Born 1870, Jan., 29."
    - Lena Bourne Fish, October 1944, 1 negative: 4.25 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph030
      Location: East Jaffrey, New Hampshire. Handwritten note on reverse: "Mrs. Lena B. Fis[h]; Oct. 1944; E. Jaffrey N.H.; 'Granny'."
    - Lena Bourne Fish and a young girl, October 1944, 1 negative: 4.25 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph031
      Location: East Jaffrey, New Hampshire.
    - Serena J. Frye and Mary P. Frye (portrait 1 of 2), 1938, 1 print: gelatin silver; 3 x 5.5 in.; afc1942002_ph032
      Location: Brookline, Massachusetts. The collection contains multiple prints, in various dimensions, of this image.
    - Serena J. Frye and Mary P. Frye (portrait 2 of 2), 1938, 1 negative: 2.5 x 4.25 in.; afc1942002_ph033
      Location: Brookline, Massachusetts.
    - Carrie B. Grover, sitting on porch steps, poised to play fiddle (portrait 1 of 2), October 1943, 1 negative: 1.75 x 2.75 in.; afc1942002_ph034
      Location: Gorham, Maine. Handwritten note on reverse of one print: "Mrs. Carrie Grover; 300 family ballads plus fiddle tunes."
    - Carrie B. Grover, sitting on porch steps, poised to play fiddle (portrait 2 of 2), October 1943, 1 negative: 1.75 x 2.75 in.; afc1942002_ph035
      Location: Gorham, Maine.
    - Almon H. Grover and Carrie B. Grover (Mr. and Mrs. Grover), sitting on porch steps, October 1943, 1 negative: 1.75 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph036
    - Mrs. Gertrude Beacham Hamm, unidentified man, and Eloise Hubbard Linscott, circa 1940-1959, 1 print: gelatin silver; 4.5 x 5.75 in.; afc1942002_ph037
      Location: Laconia, New Hampshire. Handwritten note on reverse: "[??] At The Author's Tea - Laconia NH with Mrs. Gertrude Hamm."
    - Arthur W. Hanson, seated in rocking chair, holding fiddle and bow, October 28, 1945, 1 negative: 1.75 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph038
      Location: Ossipee, New Hampshire.
    - Arthur W. Hanson, seated in rocking chair, poised to play fiddle, October 28, 1945, 1 negative: 1.75 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph039
    - Arthur W. Hanson, holding fiddle and bow in right hand, opening house door with left hand, October 28, 1945, 1 negative: 1.75 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph040
      Location: Ossipee, New Hampshire. Handwritten note on back of one print: "Arthur W Hanson Oct 28 - 45 Ossipee N.H. 54 yrs old this year."
    - Val Hardy, standing on porch, poised to play fiddle, April 1951, 1 negative: 4.75 x 2.75 in.; afc1942002_ph041
      Location: Enfield, New Hampshire.
    - Val Hardy and Mrs. Val (Lillian) Hardy, standing on porch; he is holding fiddle and bow, April 1951, 1 negative: 4.5 x 2.75 in.; afc1942002_ph042
    - Mary Elwood Harmon (Ma Harmon), November 1, 1941, 1 negative: 2.5 x 1.75 in.; afc1942002_ph043
      Location: Cambridge, Massachusetts.
    - Mary Elwood Harmon (Ma Harmon), November 1, 1941, 1 negative: 2.5 x 1.75 in.; afc1942002_ph044
    - Ma Horn (Frances Horn), standing behind open front door, circa 1939, 1 negative: 4.5 x 2.75 in.; afc1942002_ph045
    - Ma Horn (Frances Horn), standing in open doorway, circa 1939, 1 negative: 4.5 x 2.75 in.; afc1942002_ph046
    - Ma Horn (Frances Horn), portrait 1 of 2, circa 1939, 1 negative: 4.5 x 2.75 in.; afc1942002_ph047
    - Ma Horn (Frances Horn), portrait 2 of 2, circa 1939, 1 negative: 4.5 x 2.75 in.; afc1942002_ph048
    - John Hutchinson in front of woodshed full of corn, November 12, 1941, 1 negative: 2.5 x 1.75 in.; afc1942002_ph049
      Location: Berry's Mills, Maine. Kittens can be seen in the photo.
    - George Andrew (Stonewall) Jackson, with Will E. Ayer's arm seen at right, April 18, 1943, 1 negative: 1.75 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph050
      Location: Concord, New Hampshire. Handwritten note on reverse: "April 18, 1943 "Stonewall" Geo. Andrew Jackson Concord NH."
    - Lee Johnson and Jennie Hardy Linscott, circa 1939, 1 negative: 4.5 x 2.75 in.; afc1942002_ph051
      Location: 36 Mayo Avenue, Needham, Massachusetts 36 Mayo Avenue was the home address of the collector and her family.
    - Edith Irons Kidder, sitting on a small mound of hay, 1940, 1 print: gelatin silver; 2.25 x 3.25 in.; afc1942002_ph052
      Location: unknown, although Kidder lived in Freetown, Massachusetts.
    - Edith Irons Kidder, seated in chair, facing camera, 1940, 1 print: gelatin silver; 3.25 x 2.25 in.; afc1942002_ph053
    - Edith Irons Kidder, seated in chair, looking to her right, 1940, 1 print: gelatin silver; 3.25 x 2.25 in.; afc1942002_ph054
    - Edwin L. (Ed) Larkin, seated on front porch steps, holding fiddle and bow, August 21, 1944, 1 print: gelatin silver; 3.25 x 2.25 in.; afc1942002_ph055
      Location: Chelsea, Vermont.
    - Edwin L. (Ed) Larkin, seated on front porch steps, poised to play fiddle (portrait 1 of 2), August 21, 1944, 1 print: gelatin silver; 3.25 x 2.25 in.; afc1942002_ph056
    - Edwin L. (Ed) Larkin, seated on front porch steps, poised to play fiddle (portrait 2 of 2), August 21, 1944, 1 negative: 4.5 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph057
    - Edwin L. (Ed) Larkin, seated on porch, poised to play fiddle (autographed greeting card), circa 1949, 1 print: gelatin silver; 5.5 x 4.25 in.; afc1942002_ph058
    - Harold Larrabee and Nathansel (Ansel) Young, November 8, 1941, 1 negative: 2.5 x 1.75 in.; afc1942002_ph059
      Location: Rockland, Maine. Handwritten note on reverse (in pen): "Nathansel Youn[g] Rockland Me. And Harold Larrabe[e] (bones player[)] 8 Nov. 1941," and in pencil: "Nathansel Young fiddler Rockland Me."
    - Newcomb Fuller or Oscar York, Lake Winnipesaukee, New Hampshire (portrait 1 of 3), 1939, 1 negative: 4.5 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph060
      Location: Lake Winnipesaukee, New Hampshire.
    - Newcomb Fuller or Oscar York, Lake Winnipesaukee, New Hampshire (portrait 2 of 3), 1939, 1 negative: 4.5 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph061
    - Newcomb Fuller or Oscar York, Lake Winnipesaukee, New Hampshire (portrait 3 of 3), 1939, 1 negative: 4.5 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph062
    - Edward A. (Ed) Lewis, holding fiddle case under left arm, July 13, 1955, 1 negative: 2.25 x 2.25 in.; afc1942002_ph063
      Location: 12 Ballard Street, Durham, New Hampshire.
    - Edward A. (Ed) Lewis, holding fiddle and bow, July 13, 1955, 1 print: gelatin silver; 3 x 3 in.; afc1942002_ph064
      Location: 12 Ballard Street, Durham, New Hampshire. Handwritten note on reverse: "Ed A. Lewis July 13- 1955 12 Ballard St Durham N.H.}
    - Edward A. (Ed) Lewis, standing outside a house, Summer 1967, 1 print: gelatin silver; 5.5 x 3 in.; afc1942002_ph065
    - Eloise Hubbard Linscott and family dog Trek, in a canoe, circa 1940-1949, 1 print: gelatin silver; 5 x 6.75 in.; afc1942002_ph066
      Location: Winter Harbor, Camp Ossipee, Wolfeboro, New Hampshire.
    - Eloise Hubbard Linscott, October 12, 1939, 1 print: gelatin silver; 4.5 x 3.5 in.; afc1942002_ph067
      Location: Camp Ossipee, Wolfeboro, New Hampshire.
    - Eloise Hubbard Linscott, posing with a saw, by a log cabin, Summer 1939, 1 print: gelatin silver; 4.5 x 3.5 in.; afc1942002_ph068
    - Eloise Hubbard Linscott, posing by a cabin, Summer 1939, 1 negative: 4.25 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph069
    - Eloise Hubbard Linscott, posing with a cradle board, May 1941, 1 negative: 1.75 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph070
      Location: Beverly, Massachusetts.
    - Eloise Hubbard Linscott, circa 1930-1939, 1 print: gelatin silver; 6 x 4 in.; afc1942002_ph071
    - Eloise Hubbard Linscott, circa 1960-1969, 1 print: gelatin silver; 6 x 4 in.; afc1942002_ph072
      Location: Wolfeboro, New Hampshire. The collection contains multiple prints of this image.
    - Eloise Hubbard Linscott (studio portrait), circa 1939, 1 negative: 4.75 x 3.5 in.; afc1942002_ph073
    - John Hubbard Linscott, with Needahbeh's war club, blanket, and eagle feather headdress (portrait 1 of 3), circa 1940s, 1 print: gelatin silver; 4 x 2.75 in.; afc1942002_ph074
      Handwritten note on reverse: "John dressed in Chief Nee dah bah's head dress of eagle feathers."
    - John Hubbard Linscott, with Needahbeh's war club, blanket, and eagle feather headdress (portrait 2 of 3), circa 1940s, 1 print: gelatin silver; 2.75 x 4 in.; afc1942002_ph075
      Handwritten note on reverse: "Nee dah bah tries on his chief's headdress to John and blanket and war club."
    - John Hubbard Linscott, with Needahbeh's war club, blanket, and eagle feather headdress (portrait 3 of 3), circa 1940s, 1 print: gelatin silver; 4 x 2.75 in.; afc1942002_ph076
    - Dennis McClure, standing on sidewalk, April 23, 1941, 1 negative: 2.5 x 1.75 in.; afc1942002_ph077
      Location: Willimantic, Connecticut. Handwritten on reverse of one print: Denny McClure caller Willimantic Conn.
    - Herbert Meatty, Maynard Meatty, William J. (Jack) Sherrard, Llewellyn S. Powers, George Andrew (Stonewall) Jackson, and Forrest Mowry (portrait 1 of 3), May 25, 1946, 1 negative: 4.5 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph078
    - Herbert Meatty, Maynard Meatty, William J. (Jack) Sherrard, Llewellyn S. Powers, George Andrew (Stonewall) Jackson, and Forrest Mowry (portrait 2 of 3), May 25, 1946, 1 negative: 2.5 x 4.25 in.; afc1942002_ph079
    - Herbert Meatty, Maynard Meatty, William J. (Jack) Sherrard, Llewellyn S. Powers, George Andrew (Stonewall) Jackson, and Forrest Mowry (portrait 3 of 3), May 25, 1946, 1 negative: 4.25 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph080
    - Metosanya, standing, with cradle board leaning against her, May 24, 1941, 1 print: gelatin silver; 1.5 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph081
      Location: 10 Bow Street, Beverly, Massachusetts.
    - Metosanya, holding cradle board (full-length portrait), May 24, 1941, 1 print: gelatin silver; 2.5 x 1.75 in.; afc1942002_ph082
    - Metosanya, holding cradle board (landscape view), May 24, 1941, 1 print: gelatin silver; 3 x 4.75 in.; afc1942002_ph083
    - Metosanya, kneeling by a cradle board, May 24, 1941, 1 print: gelatin silver; 3.75 x 2.5 in; afc1942002_ph084
    - Metosanya (studio portrait), October 1944, 1 print: gelatin silver; 3.75 x 2.5 in; afc1942002_ph085
      Photographed by Charles L. Hanson, Jr.
    - Needahbeh, standing in a clearing near a wooded area, November 2, 1945, 1 negative: 2.5 x 1.75 in.; afc1942002_ph086
      Location: Fosters Pond, North Wilmington, Massachusetts.
    - Smith Paine, seated, posing with fiddle and bow, June 1938, 1 negative: 4.25 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph087
    - Smith Paine, seated, poised to play fiddle, June 1938, 1 negative: 4.25 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph088
    - Jean Parris, seated on the ground, November 16, 1941, 1 negative: 1.75 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph089
    - Jean Parris and Leroy (Roy) Parris, November 16, 1941, 1 negative: 1.75 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph090
    - Leroy (Roy) Parris and George (Rocky Mountain George) Brown, as seen through a car window (portrait 1 of 2), November 16, 1941, 1 negative: 1.75 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph091
    - Leroy (Roy) Parris and George (Rocky Mountain George) Brown, as seen through a car window (portrait 2 of 2), November 16, 1941, 1 negative: 1.75 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph092
    - Captain David Peirce, May 1, 1940, 1 print: gelatin silver; 5.5 x 3.5 in.; afc1942002_ph093
      Location: Bourne Ship Room, Whaling Museum, Old Dartmouth Historical Society, New Bedford, Massachusetts.
    - Eloise Hubbard Linscott, Grace N. Palmer, Margaret E. (Peg) Robbins, Philip P. Sharples, Ralph Page, Louise Chapin, Patricia Parmelee, unidentified person, and Mary Gillette (members of the planning committee, Fall Folk Festival), October 28, 1944, 1 print: gelatin silver; 4.5 x 6.5 in.; afc1942002_ph094
      Location: Boston, Massachusetts.
    - Charles W. (Charlie) Potter (portrait 1 of 2), September 25, 1946, 1 negative: 4.25 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph095
      Location: Lancaster, New Hampshire.
    - Charles W. (Charlie) Potter (portrait 2 of 2), September 25, 1946, 1 negative: 4.25 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph096
    - Charles W. (Charlie) Potter and unidentified man, September 25, 1946, 1 negative: 4.25 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph097
    - Charles W. (Charlie) Potter and his grandson, undated, 1 print: 7.75 x 9.75 in.; afc1942002_ph098
      This photo was enlarged from a photomechanical print published in the Stark, New Hampshire, Bicentennial volume (as per note in Linscott's handwriting, on reverse of this photo's matte).
    - Llewellyn S. Powers, sitting on house steps, holding fiddle and bow under right arm, 1940, 1 negative: 4.25 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph099
      Location: Brookline, New Hampshire.
    - Llewellyn S. Powers, sitting on house steps, poised to play fiddle, 1940, 1 negative: 4.25 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph100
    - Fred Pullen and Frederick W. Pullen, Jr., July 1938, 1 negative: 4.25 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph101
      Location: North Anson, Maine.
    - Fred Pullen, Mrs. Fred (Vivian) Pullen, and Frederick W. Pullen, Jr., July 1938, 1 negative: 4.25 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph102
    - Albert Quigley (with fiddle and bow), sons Terrance (Terry) and Barnabas (Barney), daughter Thomasa (Tami), and wife Mildred Quigley, probably November 11, 1944, 1 negative: 2.5 x 4.25 in.; afc1942002_ph103
      Location: Nelson, New Hampshire.
    - Cassius (Cash) Radford, seated, holding a baby (portrait 1 of 2), July 1938, 1 negative: 4.25 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph104
      Location: according to Folk Songs of New England, Radford lived in Pembroke, New Hampshire, although other records note him as a longtime resident of Conford, New Hampshire.
    - Cassius (Cash) Radford, seated, holding a baby (portrait 2 of 2), July 1938, 1 negative: 4.25 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph105
    - Mable Johnson Hunter, Maynard Reynolds, and Mrs. Maynard Reynolds (portrait 1 of 2), March 1943, 1 negative: 2.5 x 1.75 in.; afc1942002_ph106
      Location: 44 Brown Street, Wickford, Rhode Island. Photographed at the home (as of March 1943) of Mrs. and Mrs. Maynard Reynolds. See ph107 and ph185 for similar images.
    - Mable Johnson Hunter, Maynard Reynolds, and Mrs. Maynard Reynolds (portrait 2 of 2), March 1943, 1 negative: 1.75 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph107
    - Roger Robinson and his son Roland Robinson, each posing with fiddle and bow, probably November 7, 1941, 1 negative: 2.5 x 1.75 in.; afc1942002_ph108
      Location: Bowdoinham, Maine.
    - Roger Robinson and his son Roland Robinson, each poised to play fiddle, probably November 7, 1941, 1 negative: 2.5 x 1.75 in.; afc1942002_ph109
    - The Shaker Singers, of Enfield, New Hampshire, August 1948, 1 negative: 2.25 x 3.5 in.; afc1942002_ph110
      Location: Enfield, New Hampshire. The Shaker Singers were founded to keep Shaker folklore and singing traditions alive, although none of the members were Shaker.
    - William J. (Jack) Sherrard (portrait 1 of 2), October 1943, 1 negative: 2.5 x 1.75 in.; afc1942002_ph111
      Location: Munsonville, New Hampshire.
    - William J. (Jack) Sherrard (portrait 2 of 2), October 1943, 1 negative: 2.5 x 1.75 in.; afc1942002_ph112
    - William J. (Jack) Sherrard, at the four-mile sign for Mystic Marine Museum, June 2, 1950, 1 negative: 4.25 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph113
      Location: Connecticut.
    - William J. (Jack) Sherrard, standing on the dock by the Joseph Conrad, at the Mystic Marine Museum, June 2, 1950, 1 negative: 4.25 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph114
      Location: Mystic Seaport, Mystic, Connecticut.
    - Unidentified man and William J. (Jack) Sherrard, at the Mystic Marine Museum (portrait 1 of 2), June 2, 1950, 1 negative: 4.25 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph115
      Location: Mystic Seaport, Mystic, Connecticut. Handwritten note on print reverse: "2 sail trained men."
    - Unidentified man and William J. (Jack) Sherrard, at the Mystic Marine Museum (portrait 2 of 2), June 2, 1950, 1 negative: 4.25 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph116
      Location: Mystic Seaport, Mystic, Connecticut. Handwritten note on print reverse: "2 windjammer deep water man [sic]."
    - William J. (Jack) Sherrard, 1954, 1 color print: dye coupler; 3 x 3 in.; afc1942002_ph117
      Location: Needham, Massachusetts. Handwritten note on reverse: "W.J. Sherrard 1954 at Needham [square] rigger seaman." The collector and her family lived in Needham.
    - William J. (Jack) Sherrard, on the bridge leading to his house (portrait 1 of 2), May 1965, 1 color print: dye coupler; 4.5 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph118
    - William J. (Jack) Sherrard, on the bridge leading to his house (portrait 2 of 2), May 1965, 1 color print: dye coupler; 4.5 x 2.; afc1942002_ph119
    - William J. (Jack) Sherrard, his roommate (at left), and his roommate's dog, 1965, 1 color negative: safety; 4.5 x 2.5; afc1942002_ph120
    - William J. (Jack) Sherrard, November 20, 1965, 1 color negative: safety; 4.5 x 2.5; afc1942002_ph121
      Location: 36 Mayo Avenue, Needham, Massachusetts. Handwritten note on reverse: "Old Jack on the way back to Munsonville, NH." The collector and her family lived in Needham.
    - William J. (Jack) Sherrard and his house, circa 1960-1969, 1 color print (double exposure): dye coupler; 5.5 x 3 in.; afc1942002_ph122
      Location: Munsonville, New Hampshire. The image is a double exposure, depicting Sherrard and his house. Linscott's handwritten note on reverse: "How to get to Jack's house in Munsonville, N.H. over a brook up a plank around and behind house up another plank and IF the string is outside, open the door. If it's inside - knock. Knock anyway and yoo-hoo!"
    - Captain Charlton Lyman Smith, outdoors, 1938-1940, 1 negative: 4.25 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph123
      Location: Marblehead, Massachusetts.
    - Captain Charlton Lyman Smith, indoors, 1938-1940, 1 negative: 4.25 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph124
    - William (Bill) Spink, playing the fiddle (portrait 1 of 2), October 1944, 1 negative: 4.25 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph125
      Location: Chepachet, Rhode Island.
    - William (Bill) Spink, playing the fiddle (portrait 2 of 2), October 1944, 1 negative: 4.25 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph126
    - William (Bill) Spink and an unidentified woman, October 1944, 1 negative: 4.25 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph127
    - Gene Staples, holding fiddle and bow, leaning against a piano, undated, 1 negative: 4.25 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph128
      Location: possibly Dixfield, Maine. Linscott's handwritten note on reverse: "Champion Old Time fiddl[er] 1936 State of Maine [a]ddress: Dixfield Maine."
    - Gene Staples, holding fiddle and bow, standing between two unidentified women, undated, 1 print: gelatin silver; 5.25 x 3.25 in; afc1942002_ph129
      Location: possibly Dixfield, Maine.
    - Three Shaker sisters, undated, 1 negative: safety; 2.25 x 3.25 in.; afc1942002_ph130
      Location: Canterbury, New Hampshire.
    - Three Shaker sisters (at left), plus an unidentified woman, undated, 1 negative: safety; 2.25 x 3.25 in.; afc1942002_ph131
    - Sam (Sammy) Tomah and Sebatias (Sebat) Tomah (portrait 1 of 2), circa September-October 1947, 1 negative: 3.25 x 2.25 in.; afc1942002_ph132
      Location: Peter Dana Point, Princeton, Maine. According to Linscott's field notes, Sammy and Sebat are cousins.
    - Sam (Sammy) Tomah and Sebatias (Sebat) Tomah (portrait 2 of 2), circa September-October 1947, 1 negative: 3.25 x 2.25 in.; afc1942002_ph133
      Location: Peter Dana Point, Princeton, Maine. According to Linscott's field notes, Sammy and Sebat are cousins. Handwritten note on reverse of one photo names "Princeton, Maine" as the location.
    - Uncle Abe's Mountain Rangers, undated, 1 print: gelatin silver; 3.5 x 5.5 in.; afc1942002_ph134
      Handwritten note on reverse: "This is the band we had a year ago, we used to play on the radio over Station W.L.N.H. used to have one hour on the air--I have marked my husband and myself picture. I did the announcing and also prompted (or called the dances. Mrs. Hobbs. (Auntie Abe.)."
    - Mr. Wadsworth (portrait 1 of 3), April 16, 1941, 1 print: gelatin silver; 3.5 x 5.5 in.; afc1942002_ph135
      Location: Farmington, Connecticut.
    - Mr. Wadsworth (portrait 2 of 3), April 16, 1941, 1 print: gelatin silver; 1.5 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph136
    - Mr. Wadsworth (portrait 3 of 3), April 16, 1941, 1 negative: 1.75 x 2.75 in.; afc1942002_ph137
    - Abraham (Abe) Washburn, with his grandson and granddaughter, September 27, 1946, 1 negative: 4.25 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph138
      Location: Kidderville, New Hampshire.
    - Willie (Bill) Woodward (portrait 1 of 2), 1938, 1 negative: 4.25 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph139
    - Willie (Bill) Woodward (portrait 2 of 2), 1938, 1 negative: 4.25 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph140
    - Sam Young, Jr.; unidentified man at left is partially obscured, May 1940, 1 negative: 4.5 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph141
      Location: Laconia, New Hampshire.
    - Leroy (Roy) Parris, waving, circa 1941, 1 negative: 4.25 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph142
    - Man, unidentified, undated, 1 negative: 2.25 x 2.25 in.; afc1942002_ph143
    - Man, unidentified, undated, 1 color negative: safety; 3.5 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph144
    - Ward Wilkins (?), undated, 1 negative: 4.5 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph145
      Location: 36 Mayo Avenue, Needham, Massachusetts. Ward Wilkins was a friend of Eloise and Charles Linscott. The address is the home of the collector and her family.
    - Native American child, unidentified, September 1947, 1 negative: 2.25 x 3.5 in.; afc1942002_ph146
      Location: Peter Dana Point, Princeton, Maine. Written in the collector's handwriting, on photo reverse: "Indian papoose at Peter Dana Poi..." (photo is cropped; writing is cut off).
    - Jennie Hardy Linscott, circa 1930s, 1 print: gelatin silver; 3.75 x 2.5 in.; afc1942002_ph147